How we track
AI visibility
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
we also have an
AI visibility
tracker that we
built with AI but
we use a data
source called
DataForSEO and so
we pull directly
from it So every
person in that
service area
it will go for
each one of the
top four
platforms and
actually pull
real queries
So it will really
actually do a
search as if it
was asking the
question about
septic services
in that specific
area
And then it gives
us the list of
who's showing up
first
second
third
fourth
fifth
sixth
And so we have
that list for all
of our clients
We track that our
clients get a
dashboard and
they have an AI
visibility
tracker on there
It shows where
they're
performing in
comparison with
their
competitors
And I think our
clients are
pretty much all
dominating that I
can think of